pegperego.com 2014-11-28

# Privacy Policy | Italian-made baby products and riding toys | Peg Perego

At Peg Perego, we take your right to privacy seriously. We want you to feel comfortable using our website. This privacy policy deals with personal identifiable information (referred to as “data” below) that may be collected by us on our site. This policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control. Please take time to read our terms of use.

##  Collection of Data

Our registration process requires only a valid email address and a name. Providing us with other information is your option. Like many websites, we may also automatically receive general information that is contained in our server log files, such as your IP address and cookie information. Information about how advertising may be served on this site (if at all) is set forth below.

##  Use of Data

We may use data to customize and improve your user experience on this site. We will make efforts so that your data will not be provided to third parties unless (1) Provided for otherwise in this privacy policy; (2) We obtain your consent, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out to the sharing of data; (3) A service provided on our site requires the interaction with (or is provided by) a third party, by way of example, an application service provider; (4) Pursuant to legal process or law enforcement; (5) We find that your use of this site violates this policy, terms of service, other usage guidelines or as deemed reasonable or necessary for us to protect our legal rights and/or property; (6) (or) This site is purchased by a third party whereby that third party will be able to use the data in the same manner as we set forth in this policy. In the event you choose to use links that appear on our site to other websites, you are advised to read the privacy policy that appears on those sites.

##  Cookies

Like many websites, we set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings. Advertisements may appear on our website and, if so, they set and access cookies on your computer and are subject to the privacy policy of those parties providing the advertisements. However, the companies serving the advertising do not have access to our cookies. These companies usually use non-personally identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visit to our site.

##  Children

We do not allow persons who are thirteen or younger to become members of this site. For more information, please contact our webmaster.

##  Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may make changes to this policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantial changes to this policy either by posting a prominent announcement on our site or by sending a message to the email address you have provided to us that is contained within your user settings.

##  Visiting Other Websites

From time to time, we may offer links to websites belonging to third parties. We are not responsible for these non-Peg Perego websites, and you enter them at your own risk. Your personal information is protected as described in that website's privacy policy.
